// Array of questions with options and correct answers
const questions = [
{
    numb: 71,
    question: 'I was alarmed_______his death.',
    answer: 'at',
    options: [
      'by',
      'at',
      'upon',
      'from'
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 72,
    question: 'What did you make ____ the lecture?',
    answer: 'of',
    options: [
      'of',
      'in',
      'about',
      'on'
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 73,
    question: 'The teacher set some homework ____ the end of the lesson.',
    answer: 'at',
    options: [
      'of',
      'in',
      'about',
      'at'
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 74,
    question: 'He writes _____ ink.',
    answer: 'in',
    options: [
      'WITH',
      'IN',
      'FOR',
      'ON'
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 75,
    question: 'If ____ the match, I will go to “KPK (Peshawar) to meet the sports board chairperson.',
    answer: 'I win',
    options: [
      'I will win',
      'I win',
      'I wins',
      'I shall win'
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 76,
    question: 'I have been working here ____ ten years.',
    answer: 'for',
    options: [
      'from',
      'since',
      'for',
      'with'
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 77,
    question: 'I suspect him ____ stealing the pen.',
    answer: 'of',
    options: [
      'for',
      'of',
      'over',
      'on'
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 78,
    question: 'My brother was trembling ____ cold.',
    answer: 'with',
    options: [
      'from',
      'with',
      'of',
      'by'
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 79,
    question: 'He is worried ____ his future.',
    answer: 'about',
    options: [
      'for',
      'of',
      'about',
      'with'
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 80,
    question: 'They are anxious ____ his health.',
    answer: 'about',
    options: [
      'for',
      'at',
      'about',
      'on'
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 81,
    question: 'She is thankful to you for being so patient ____ her.',
    answer: 'with',
    options: [
      'for',
      'of',
      'with',
      'at'
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 82,
    question: 'He is weak ____ grammar.',
    answer: 'in',
    options: [
      'at',
      'in',
      'from',
      'with'
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 83,
    question: 'I have had problems similar ____ yours.',
    answer: 'to',
    options: [
      'from',
      'with',
      'of',
      'to'
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 84,
    question: 'I am sick ____ job.',
    answer: 'of',
    options: [
      'from',
      'with',
      'of',
      'by'
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 85,
    question: 'He is averse ____ hard work.',
    answer: 'to',
    options: [
      'on',
      'to',
      'at',
      'from'
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 86,
    question: 'Unfortunately, we had to cancel it owing ____ the bad weather.',
    answer: 'to',
    options: [
      'of',
      'in',
      'about',
      'to'
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 87,
    question: 'She suffers ____ a heart disease.',
    answer: 'from',
    options: [
      'from',
      'in',
      'about',
      'on'
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 88,
    question: 'The food is very good ____ that restaurant.',
    answer: 'in',
    options: [
      'at',
      'of',
      'in',
      'with'
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 89,
    question: 'You must bear ____ his pranks.',
    answer: 'with',
    options: [
      'with',
      'in',
      'some of',
      'all'
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 90,
    question: 'There is no point ____ arguing.',
    answer: 'in',
    options: [
      'to',
      'from',
      'in',
      'on'
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 91,
    question: 'The prisoner was bound _____ the stake.',
    answer: 'to',
    options: [
      'with',
      'on',
      'to',
      'a'
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 92,
    question: 'Prime Minister has arrived ____ London.',
    answer: 'in',
    options: [
      'at',
      'from',
      'in',
      'none'
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 93,
    question: 'She is interested _____ drawing and painting.',
    answer: 'in',
    options: [
      'of',
      'on',
      'in',
      'with'
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 94,
    question: 'There is still no cure ____ AIDS.',
    answer: 'for',
    options: [
      'of',
      'to',
      'for',
      'with'
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 95,
    question: 'Sana was staring ____ me.',
    answer: 'at',
    options: [
      'to',
      'towards',
      'at',
      'on'
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 96,
    question: 'Sana is popular ____ her friends.',
    answer: 'with',
    options: [
      'among',
      'by',
      'over',
      'with'
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 97,
    question: 'The training session has been changed from 9:00 _____ 10:00.',
    answer: 'to',
    options: [
      'at',
      'to',
      'in',
      'by'
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 98,
    question: 'Amna was engaged ____ Asim.',
    answer: 'to',
    options: [
      'with',
      'from',
      'to',
      'none'
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 99,
    question: 'I’m ____ sure of it as you are.',
    answer: 'as',
    options: [
      'quite',
      'as',
      'perfectly',
      'very'
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 100,
    question: 'It was kind ____ you to help.',
    answer: 'of',
    options: [
      'of',
      'in',
      'about',
      'on'
    ]
  }
  
]
